Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      Series contains vinyl discs that are either not annotated or the annotations are small and were missed during the sorting of discs. While some effort was taken to bring together piences that were dense in copy-specific track preferences. These items are arranged in alphabetical order by artists’ last name or the name of the group. Each letter of the alphabet has a subseries. Compilations, soundtracks, and other albums with various artists are in subseries together. Artists and groups whose names start with a number are in a separate subseries. Most artists are alphabetized under the name they are most well-known as (e.g. Puff Daddy; Prince; Fela). The variations of names are contained in the Creator field. In a few cases, however, artists’ aliases were unknown, and they may have been listed under two different artist names.
      - G
        - G., Anne - Love's here, 1989; SR-14307; G., Anne (Box 274)
          Catalog # PR 2923; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-57630-1
          Atlantic
          New York, New York
        - G-Dep - Let's get it (remix), 2001; SR-14308; G-Dep; Kain; Curry, Mark; Loon; P. Diddy (Box 274)
          Catalog # BBDP-9414; A-side Matrix # BBDP-9414-SA B
          Bad Boy Entertainment
        - G-Dep - Let's get it (remix), 2000; SR-14309; G-Dep; P. Diddy; Black Rob (Box 274)
          In same jacket as # SR-14310. Different discs.
          Catalog # 78612-79383-1; A-side Matrix # 78612-79383-1SA
        - 112 - Peaches & cream; Dance with me, 2001; SR-14310; 112 (Box 274)
          In same jacket as # SR-14309. Different discs.
          Catalog # 78612-79387-1; A-side Matrix # 78612-79387-1-SA
        - G-Dep - Special delivery; Child of the ghetto, 2001; SR-14311; G-Dep (Box 274)
          Catalog # 78612-79409-1; A-side Matrix # 78612-79409-SA
        - G-Five - Keep it on, 1983; SR-14312; G-Five (Box 274)
          Catalog # NR-1001; A-side Matrix # NR-1001-A
          Novarro
          Lansdowne, Pennsylvania
        - G-Force - Feel the force, 1983; SR-14313; G-Force; Ronnie Gee; Captain Cee (Box 274)
          Catalog # SM-12-4061; A-side Matrix # SM-12-4061 WC
          SMI
        - G, Frankie - Remember, 2003; SR-14314; G, Frankie (Box 274)
          Catalog # JM-07; A-side Matrix # JM 07 A1
          Juicy Music
          United Kingdom
        - G., Kenny - Duotones, 1986; SR-14315; G., Kenny (Box 274)
          Catalog # AL-8427; A-side Matrix # AL-8427-SA-RE1-ALD2
          Arista
        - G-Man - Treat me right, SR-14316; G-Man (Box 274)
          Annotated.
          Catalog # PRO-65; A-side Matrix # PA-10-76
          Select Records
        - G-Man - Running 2 u, 1998; SR-14317; G-Man (Box 274)
          In same jacket as # SR-14318. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # PRO 73; A-side Matrix # RUNNING2U GMAN
        - G-Man - Running 2 u, 1998; SR-14318; G-Man (Box 274)
          In same jacket as # SR-14317. Multiple copies.
        - G-Man - Running 2 u, 1998; SR-14319; G-Man (Box 274)
        - G-Mo - Ballin', 1995; SR-14320; G-Mo (Box 274)
          Catalog # 72445-14223-1; A-side Matrix # 72445-14223-1-A
          Watch It Records
        - G-Mo - Ballin', 1995; SR-14321; G-Mo (Box 274)
        - G-Mo - Ballin', 1995; SR-14322; G-Mo (Box 274)
        - G-Mo - Ballin', 1995; SR-14323; G-Mo (Box 274)
        - G-Ratz - Let's get it started, 1997; SR-14324; G-Ratz (Box 274)
          In same jacket as # SR-14325. Multiple copies. Not in discogs
          Catalog # PRO-A-8859; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-8859-A-SRR
          Qwest Records
          Burbank, California
        - G-Ratz - Let's get it started, 1997; SR-14325; G-Ratz (Box 274)
          In same jacket as # SR-14324. Multiple copies. Not in discogs
        - G-Shorties - Now who could it be?, SR-14326; G-Shorties (Box 274)
          Catalog # SR 1007; A-side Matrix # SR-1007-A
          Stress Records
          Miami Lakes, Florida
        - G-Shorties - Click, 1995; SR-14327; G-Shorties (Box 274)
          Catalog # SR 1008; A-side Matrix # SR-1009-1A
        - G-Shorties - Click, 1995; SR-14328; G-Shorties (Box 274)
        - G-Slimm - Four's Deuce's & Tray's, 1994; SR-14329; G-Slimm (Box 274)
          Catalog # BB0010LP; A-side Matrix # BB-0010-A
          Big Boy Records
          Los Angeles, California
        - G, Tony - Tony's song, 1988; SR-14330; G, Tony (Box 274)
          Catalog # Mic 506; A-side Matrix # Mic-506 A
          Micmac Records, Inc.
        - G, Warren - I want it all (Disc one), 1999; SR-14331; G, Warren (Box 274)
          In same jacket as # SR-14332. Double album.
          Catalog # 73710-1; A-side Matrix # 01-877-73710-1 A
          Restless Records
        - G, Warren - I want it all (Disc two), 1999; SR-14332; G, Warren (Box 274)
          Catalog # 73710-1; A-side Matrix # 01-877-73710-1 C
        - G, Warren - I want it all, 1999; SR-14333; G, Warren (Box 274)
          Catalog # 73721-1; A-side Matrix # 73721-1 A
        - G, Warren - This DJ, 1994; SR-14334; G, Warren (Box 274)
          Catalog # PRO 1127-1; A-side Matrix # PRO-1127-1-A
          Rush Associated Labels
        - G-Wiz - Teddy bear, 1993; SR-14335; G-Wiz (Box 274)
          Catalog # 72392 75360-1; A-side Matrix # 72392-75360-1
          Scotti Bros. Records
          Santa Monica, California
        - G-Wiz - Y-U-Doggin me, 1994; SR-14336; G-Wiz (Box 274)
          Catalog # SBAB 75388-1; A-side Matrix # SBAB-75388-1-A
        - Gab - Icy rollie; Ride wit me, 2002; SR-14337; Gab (Box 274)
          Catalog # BBM 001; A-side Matrix # BBM-001A
          Big Brother Music
          Englewood, New Jersey
        - Gablz - Shookie shookie (gimme some of your sweet cookie), 1996; SR-14338; Gablz (Box 274)
          Catalog # PRO-A-8323; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-8323-A-SR1
          Warner Bros. Music
        - Gablz - Shookie shookie (gimme some of your sweet cookie), 1996; SR-14339; Gablz (Box 274)
        - Gabriel, Peter - Security, 1982; SR-14340; Gabriel, Peter (Box 274)
          Catalog # GHS 2011; A-side Matrix # GHS-1-2011-RE1-SH2
          Geffen Records
        - Gabriel, Peter - Big time, 1986; SR-14341; Gabriel, Peter (Box 274)
          Catalog # 0-20600; A-side Matrix # 0-20600-A-SH-1
        - Gabriel, Peter - Sledgehammer, 1986; SR-14342; Gabriel, Peter (Box 274)
          Catalog # 0-20456; A-side Matrix # 0-20456-RE-1-A-SH-1
        - Gabriel, Peter - Shock the monkey; I have the touch; Kiss of life, 1982; SR-14343; Gabriel, Peter (Box 274)
          Catalog # PRO-A-1062; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-102-S
        - Gabrielle - Baby I've changed, 1996; SR-14344; Gabrielle (Box 274)
          Catalog # GAB 99; A-side Matrix # DFI 96-7 GAB 99 A1
          Go! Beat
        - Gabrielle - I wish, 1994; SR-14345; Gabrielle (Box 274)
          Catalog # 857 521-1; A-side Matrix # 857-521-1A
          London Records
        - Gage, Yvonne - Love's gonna pay you back, 1983; SR-14346; Gage, Yvonne (Box 274)
          Catalog # 4Z9 04117; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-04117-3-1B
          Chycago International Music
        - Gaimboiz - Money (the root of all evil), 1995; SR-14347; Gaimboiz (Box 274)
          Catalog # 72392 78016-1; A-side Matrix # 72392-78016-1-A
          Street Life Records
        - Gaines, Reg. E. - Please don't take my Air Jordans, 1994; SR-14348; Gaines, Reg. E. (Box 274)
          Catalog # PRO 1101-1; A-side Matrix # PRO-1101-1-A
          Mercury
        - Gaines, Reg. E. - Please don't take my Air Jordans, 1994; SR-14349; Gaines, Reg. E. (Box 274)
        - Gaines, Rosie - I surrender, 1997; SR-14350; Gaines, Rosie (Box 274)
          Catalog # 12BBANG2; A-side Matrix # 12BBANG2A
          Bigbang Records
        - Gaines, Rosie - Crazy, 1987; SR-14351; Gaines, Rosie (Box 274)
          Catalog # EAS 02608; A-side Matrix # XSS-174020-1A
          Epic
        - Gaines, Rosie - Closer than close, 1997; SR-14352; Gaines, Rosie (Box 274)
          Catalog # 12 BBANG 1; A-side Matrix # 12 BBANG 1 A2
        - Gaines, Rosie - Clean up woman, 1990; SR-14353; Gaines, Rosie (Box 274)
          Catalog # M 522; A-side Matrix # M 522-A
          !Hype
          Germany
        - Gainsbourg - Love on the beat, 1984; SR-14354; Gainsbourg (Box 274)
          Catalog # 822 849-1; A-side Matrix # 001 822849 1
          Philips
          France
        - Gajraj, Terry - Boom Terry, 1998; SR-14355; Gajraj, Terry (Box 274)
          Not in discogs
          Catalog # JMC 1196; A-side Matrix # JMC-1196-A
          Jamaican me Crazy
          Richmond Hill, New York
        - Gala - Graduale, 1994; SR-14356; Gala (Box 274)
          Catalog # PRO 1165-1; A-side Matrix # UX-VO-NIC
          Mercury Latino
        - Gale, Eric - I know that's right; We'll make it (sooner or later), 1983; SR-14357; Gale, Eric (Box 274)
          Catalog # ED 4927; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-4927A-2
          Elektra Musician
        - Gall, France - Babacar, 1987; SR-14358; Gall, France (Box 275)
          Catalog # 242 096-1; A-side Matrix # 242096-1-A3
          Apache
        - Gallagher, Chris - Can U feel it, 1998; SR-13794; Gallagher, Chris; DJ X (Box 275)
          Catalog # XR005; A-side Matrix # XR-005-A
          Xquizit Records
          Sebring, Florida
        - Galliano - Jus' reach, 1991; SR-14359; Galliano (Box 275)
          Catalog # 162-440 552-1; A-side Matrix # 162-440-5522-1AS-SP
          4th & Broadway
        - Galliano - Jus' reach, 1991; SR-14360; Galliano (Box 275)
        - Galliano - Welcome to the story, 1990; SR-14361; Galliano (Box 275)
          Catalog # TLKX3; A-side Matrix # TLK 3A-1U-1-1
          Talkin' Loud
        - Galliano - Jus' reach, 1991; SR-14362; Galliano (Box 275)
        - Galliano, Frederic - The african divas part 2, 2002; SR-14363; Galliano, Frederic (Box 275)
          Catalog # F 153 W2; A-side Matrix # B260288-01 A1
          F Communications
        - Game - Gotta take your love; You and me, 1982; SR-14364; Game (Box 275)
          Catalog # TAS-2802E; A-side Matrix # TAS-2802-E-A
          Peter Pan Artists Series
          Newark, New Jersey
        - Game - How we do, 2004; SR-14365; Game; 50 Cent (Box 275)
          Catalog # B0003913-11; A-side Matrix # INTR-11270-1A RE1
          Aftermath Entertainment
        - Game - How we do, 2004; SR-14366; Game; 50 Cent (Box 275)
        - Gang Of Four - Another day/Another dollar, 1982; SR-14367; Gang Of Four (Box 275)
          In same jacket as # SR-14368. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # MINI 3646; A-side Matrix # MINI-1-3646-RE1-WW1
          Warner Bros. Records
        - Gang Of Four - Another day/Another dollar, 1982; SR-14368; Gang Of Four (Box 275)
          In same jacket as # SR-14367. Multiple copies.
        - Gang Of Four - To hell with poverty, 1981; SR-14369; Gang Of Four (Box 275)
          Catalog # 12EMI5193; A-side Matrix # 12EMI5193A-1U
          EMI
          London, United Kingdom
        - Gang Of Four - Another day/Another dollar, 1982; SR-14370; Gang Of Four (Box 275)
        - Gang Of Four - I love a man in uniform, 1982; SR-14371; Gang Of Four (Box 275)
          In same jacket as # SR-14372. Different discs.
          Catalog # 0-29907; A-side Matrix # 0-29907-4-SH1
        - Gang Of Four - I love a man in uniform, 1982; SR-14372; Gang Of Four (Box 275)
          In same jacket as # SR-14371. Different discs.
        - Gang Of Four - Is it love, 1983; SR-14373; Gang Of Four (Box 275)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2081; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-1-2081-SH1
        - Gang Starr - Believe dat!, 1987; SR-14374; Gang Starr (Box 275)
          Catalog # WP1004; A-side Matrix # WP-1004-1
          Wild Pitch Records
        - Gang Starr - The lesson, 1987; SR-14375; Gang Starr (Box 275)
          Catalog # NU7170; A-side Matrix # NU-7170-A
        - Gang Starr - Suckas need bodyguards, 1994; SR-14376; Gang Starr (Box 275)
          Catalog # Y-58265; A-side Matrix # Y-58265-A
          Chrysalis
          Hollywood, California
        - Gang Starr - You know my steez, 1997; SR-14377; Gang Starr (Box 275)
          Different jacket
          Catalog # SPRO-12752; A-side Matrix # SPRO-12752-A
          Noo Trybe Records
        - Ganga Kru - Super sharp shooter, 1996; SR-14378; Ganga Kru (Box 275)
          Catalog # KRU1; A-side Matrix # KRU-1-A
          Parousia
        - Gang's Back - Hot fun, 1981; SR-14379; Gang's Back (Box 275)
          In same jacket as # SR-14380. Different discs.
          Catalog # 4W9 02626; A-side Matrix # 4W9-2626
          Handshake Records and Tapes
        - Gang's Back - Hot fun, 1981; SR-14380; Gang's Back (Box 275)
          In same jacket as # SR-14379. Different discs.
          Catalog # WS9 02625; A-side Matrix # WS-902625-AS-T1
        - Gangsta Boo - Where dem dollas at, 1998; SR-14381; Gangsta Boo (Box 275)
          Catalog # RPROLP0821; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-0821A MB
          Relativity
          Jamaica, New York
        - Gant - El Gant, 2001; SR-14382; Gant (Box 275)
          Catalog # 54450-0; A-side Matrix # PR-54450-4RE1
          B-Town Records
          United States
        - Ganzie, Terry - Treat the woman right; King of kings, 1994; SR-14383; Ganzie, Terry (Box 275)
          Catalog # PRO-7422-0-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7422DJA
          Profile Records
        - Ganzie, Terry - Treat the woman right; King of kings, 1994; SR-14384; Ganzie, Terry (Box 275)
        - Gap Band - Straight from the heart, 1988; SR-14385; Gap Band (Box 275)
          Catalog # TED 1003; A-side Matrix # TED 1003-1
          Total Experience Records
        - Gap Band - Going in circles, 1986; SR-14386; Gap Band (Box 275)
          Catalog # TED1-2632; A-side Matrix # TED1-2632-AS-RE1-2
        - Gap Band - Early in the morning, 1982; SR-14387; Gap Band (Box 275)
          Catalog # TED-701; A-side Matrix # TED-701
        - Gap Band - Baby baba boogie; Shake, 1979; SR-14388; Gap Band (Box 275)
          Catalog # MK-86; A-side Matrix # MK-86-A1
        - Gap Band - Party Lights, 1979; SR-14389; Gap Band (Box 275)
          Catalog # MK-138; A-side Matrix # MK-138-RE-A2-56043
        - Gap Band - We can make it alright, 1990; SR-14390; Gap Band (Box 275)
          Catalog # V-15560; A-side Matrix # V-1-15560 Z-2
          Capitol Records
        - Gap Band - Desire, 1985; SR-14391; Gap Band (Box 275)
          Catalog # TED1-2624; A-side Matrix # TED1-2624-AS-1
        - Gap Band - Zibble, zibble (get the money) (aka: get loose, get funky), 1986; SR-14392; Gap Band (Box 275)
          Catalog # 2705-1-TD; A-side Matrix # 2705-1-TD-AS-1
        - Gap Band - Gap Band IV, 1982; SR-14393; Gap Band (Box 275)
          Catalog # TE-1-3001; A-side Matrix # TE-1-3001-SA-2
        - Gap Band - Jammin' in America; Burn rubber on me; Oops up side your head, 1983; SR-14394; Gap Band (Box 275)
          Catalog # TEX 6; A-side Matrix # TEX6A
        - Gap Band - First lover (special house mixes), 1995; SR-14395; Gap Band (Box 275)
          Catalog # RB-8013; A-side Matrix # RB-8013-A
          Raging Bull Records
        - Gap Band - Big fun (new remix), 1986; SR-14396; Gap Band (Box 275)
          Catalog # 2701-1-TD; A-side Matrix # 2701-1-TD-AS-2
        - Gap Band - Jam the motha', 1983; SR-14397; Gap Band (Box 275)
          Catalog # TK 255; A-side Matrix # TK-255-257654-PRC-C-1-1-1 A
        - Gap Band - Jam the motha', 1983; SR-14398; Gap Band (Box 275)
        - Gap Band - Big fun (new remix), 1986; SR-14399; Gap Band (Box 275)
        - Gap Band - Burn rubber on me (why you wanna hurt me), 1980; SR-14400; Gap Band (Box 275)
          Catalog # MK 161; A-side Matrix # MK-161-2-56219-LONG-RE-1-1-1
          Chicago, Illinois
        - Gap Band - Gap Band VIII, 1986; SR-14401; Gap Band (Box 275)
          Catalog # FL 82700; A-side Matrix # DM B-6860 A-1/12-86 II
        - Gap Band - You dropped a bomb on me, 1982; SR-14402; Gap Band (Box 275)
          Catalog # TED 702; A-side Matrix # TED-702-A-
        - Gap Band - Addicted to your love, 1989; SR-14403; Gap Band (Box 275)
          Catalog # V-15534; A-side Matrix # V-1-15534 RE-1 Z-1
        - Garbage - I think I'm paranoid (Disc one), 1998; SR-14404; Garbage (Box 275)
          In same jacket as # SR-14405. Double album. Annotated.
          Catalog # TRASH23; A-side Matrix # DFI-98 6 TRASH 23 A1
          Mushroom
        - Garbage - I think I'm paranoid (Disc two), 1998; SR-14405; Garbage (Box 275)
          In same jacket as # SR-14404. Double album. Annotated.
          Catalog # TRASH23; A-side Matrix # DFI-98 6 TRASH 23 C1
        - Garbage - When I grow up, 1998; SR-14406; Garbage (Box 275)
          Catalog # TRASH29; A-side Matrix # TRASH 29-A1
        - Gardner, Stu - And the sanctified sound, 1974; SR-14407; Gardner, Stu (Box 275)
          Catalog # VOS-9503; A-side Matrix # VOS-9503 VS-0573
          Volt
        - Gardner, Taana - Work that body, 1979; SR-14408; Gardner, Taana (Box 275)
          Catalog # WE 22116; A-side Matrix # 22116A
          West End Records
        - Gardner, Taana - Work that body, 2000; SR-14409; Gardner, Taana (Box 275)
          Catalog # WES 1002; A-side Matrix # WES-1002-80001
        - Gardner, Taana - When you touch me, 1979; SR-14410; Gardner, Taana (Box 275)
          Catalog # WES 22122; A-side Matrix # 70397-22122-107-1
        - Garfield, Paul - In the universe of love, 1988; SR-14411; Garfield, Paul (Box 275)
          Catalog # TA 002; A-side Matrix # TA 002 A
          Twist Again Records
          Italy
        - Garnier, Laurent - Greed - world wide re-works (Disc one), 2000; SR-14412; Garnier, Laurent (Box 275)
          In same jacket as # SR-14413. Double album.
          Catalog # F 127 LTD; A-side Matrix # F127 LTD A
        - Garnier, Laurent - Greed - world wide re-works (Disc two), 2000; SR-14413; Garnier, Laurent (Box 275)
          In same jacket as # SR-14412. Double album.
          Catalog # F 127 LTD; A-side Matrix # F127 LTD C
        - Garnier, Laurent - Greed, 2000; SR-14414; Garnier, Laurent (Box 276)
          Catalog # F 127; A-side Matrix # DFI 00 8 F 127 A
        - Garnier, Laurent - As french connection, 1991; SR-14415; Garnier, Laurent; Mix Master Doody (Box 276)
          Catalog # 591037; A-side Matrix # 591 037 A
          Fnac Music Dance Division
        - Garrett, Ronnie - Winning team, 1985; SR-14416; Garrett, Ronnie (Box 276)
          Catalog # AC1001-12; A-side Matrix # AC-101-12-A
          Atlanta Connection Records
          Atlanta, Georgia
        - Garrett, Siedah - K.I.S.S.I.N.G., 1988; SR-14417; Garrett, Siedah (Box 276)
          Catalog # 0-20912; A-side Matrix # 0 20912 A SH2
        - Garnett, Carlos - It's summertime, 1983; SR-14418; Garnett, Carlos (Box 276)
          Catalog # TOP-006; A-side Matrix # TOP 006A
          Top Flight Records
        - Gary Toms Empire - Sexy lady, 1982; SR-14419; Gary Toms Empire (Box 276)
          Catalog # CHDS 2527; A-side Matrix # CHDS-2527-A
          Chaz Ro
        - Gary Toms Empire - Sexy lady, 1982; SR-14420; Gary Toms Empire (Box 276)
        - Gary's Gang - Keep on dancin', 1979; SR-14421; Gary's Gang (Box 276)
          Catalog # JC 35793; A-side Matrix # AL 35793-2H
          Columbia
        - Gary's Gang - Keep on dancin'; Do it at the disco, 1978; SR-14422; Gary's Gang (Box 276)
          Catalog # 23-10885; A-side Matrix # XSS-165325
        - Gary's Gang - Let's lovedance tonight; Showtime, 1979; SR-14423; Gary's Gang (Box 276)
          Catalog # AS 602; A-side Matrix # XSS-166039-1A
        - Gary's Gang - Knock me out, 1982; SR-14424; Gary's Gang (Box 276)
          Catalog # RDR-12000-DJ; A-side Matrix # RDR-12000A-DJ
          Radar Records
        - Gaston - We come to take control, 1981; SR-14425; Gaston (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14426. Different discs.
          Catalog # C.C. 120001; A-side Matrix # CC-120001